&gt；&gt；steve kinney：我想谈的其他几件事
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So a few other
things that I wanna talk about on
主题是网络负载，然后是我们提供的代码量，
the topic of network load and
then also the amount of code that we ship,
我们有越来越多的支持
is we have increasing support for
一种叫做HTTP/2的东西，令人震惊的是HTTP/1的后继者。
something called HTTP/2 which shock
surprise is the successor for HTTP/1.
而且它有一些独特的特点，对吧？
And it has some unique characteristics,
right?
再一次，这就像，我是不是应该完全优化我的策略
And again, it's like, should I
totally optimize my strategies for
一切都基于HTTP/2？
everything based on HTTP/2?
答案是，你测量你的流量，然后给你打电话，对吗？
The answer is, you measure your traffic
and then make you the call, right?
如果您没有发现有很多HTTP/2流量，
If you don't find you have
a lot of HTTP/2 traffic,
也许现在还不是时候，对吧？
maybe it's not the time yet, right?
因为我们会看到HTTP/2的很多最佳实践都是字面上的
Cuz like we're gonna see that a lot of
the best practices of HTTP/2 are literally
什么叫做HTTP/1的反模式。
what are called like
the anti-pattern to HTTP/1.
所以这是你必须做决定的事情之一。
So it's one of those things where you
have to kind of like make a decision.
有时，是否支持HTTP/2并不是由您决定的。
Sometimes whether or not you support
HTTP/2 is not your call to make.
所以举个例子，就像我说的，我们现在一堆系统上，不能
So for instance, like I said, we are on
a bunch of systems right now that don't
支持HTTP/2，我们正在向支持HTTP/2的一群移动。
support HTTP/2,
we're moving to a bunch that do.
[笑]好像那只是一件正在发生的事情，对吗？
[LAUGH] Like that's just a thing
that's happening, right?
所以我现在没有必要为他们优化，但是
So I have no point optimizing for
them now, but
这是我可能在不久的将来会做的一件事。
this is a thing that I will likely
do in the very near future.
所以这是升级。
So it's an upgrade.
最重要的是这个多路复用的想法。
The big thing is this
idea of multiplexing.
稍后我们将讨论为什么这一点很重要，并且
We'll talk about why that's
important in a second, and
而且，该服务可以在请求资产之前将资产推送到客户端，对吗？
also that service can push assets to the
client before they're asked for, right?
所以你可以理论上把它绑在一起，而不是解析HTML，
So you can kind of like theoretically tie
this in, like rather than parse the HTML,
我需要去拿CSS文件
I need to go get the CSS file.
服务器可以知道这里是HTML文件，这里是CSS文件，
The server can know here's the HTML file,
here's the CSS file,
我知道你下一个需要，现在开始服用。
I know you're gonna need next,
start taking it now.
所以，是的，它解决了我们在HTTP/1中遇到的所有问题。
So yeah, it solves all
the problem we have in HTTP/1.
我们做了很多像奇怪的黑客使HTTP/1工作。
We do a lot of like weird
hacks to make HTTP/1 work.
带宽变得更好了，但延迟却没有，
Bandwidth has gone better but
latency hasn't,
因为再一次，电子穿过行星周围的铜线，也就是
cuz like again, electrons going through
copper wire around the planet, that is
我不认为我们很快就能解决的物理问题，据我所知。
a physics problem that I don't think we're
gonna solve any time soon, that I know of.
我相信有人在做这方面的工作，但这不是我的专业领域。
I'm sure there are people working on that,
but that's not my domain of expertise.
但是使用HTTP/1，我们可以一次发送一个文件。
But with HTTP/1,
we can send one file at a time.
这意味着理论上，我会向你展示我们用来
That means while theoretically, and
I'll show you the cheat that we use for
马上就来。
this in a second.
但是您可以发送CSS文件或JavaScript文件，或者其他任何文件。
But you can send the CSS file or
the JavaScript file, or one of whatever.
因此，像将内容分解成许多小CSS文件通常不是一个好方法
So like breaking stuff up into a lot of
small CSS files is usually not a good
想法，因为你必须让任何连接都很昂贵，
idea, cuz you'd have to like
make any connections expensive,
把它们合在一起，发送过来。
jam it all together in one, send it over.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：所以它的工作方式通常是，你得到一个东西，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So the way it
works is normally, you get a thing,
你向服务器要一样东西，你就得到了。
you ask the server for
a thing, you get it.
你向服务器要一样东西，你就得到了。
You ask the server for
a thing, you get it.
就像浏览器通过打开给定的六个连接有点欺骗，并且
Like browsers cheat a little bit by they
open like six connections to a given, and
我认为这取决于浏览器的变化，Firefox可能会做八个。
I think that changes depending on
the browser, Firefox might do eight.
别引用那些数字中的任何一个。
Don't quote me on any of those numbers.
在六到八个连接之间，所以
Somewhere between six and
eight connections, so
它可以同时得到东西，对吧？
it can get stuff concurrently, right?
然后当它使用了所有的六个，它可以去得到其他的东西，但是
And then when it uses all the six and
it can go get other stuff, but
你一次六点就会筋疲力尽。
you're maxed out at six at a time.
所以我要把我的CSS分成40个文件。
So I'm gonna break my CSS into 40 files.
这不是个好主意，因为你一次只能得到六个，对吧？
That's a bad idea, because you can
only get six at a time, right?
因此，通常我们会经历这些干扰我们所有文件的过程
And so, normally we would go through these
processes of jamming all of our files
把它们连在一起，创造出这些大的，
together and concatenating them and
creating these large,
大捆，对吧？
large bundles, right?
我们在另一边看到了与之相关的某种成本
Which we've seen has a certain cost
associated with it on the other side of
管，当用户得到它。
the tube, when the user gets it.
另一方面，HTTP/2可以同时发送多个东西。
HTTP/2 on the other hand,
can send multiple things at the same time.
所以我们建立了连接，我们看到的只是抽出所有的资产，然后
So we make connections that we saw
just pumping all the assets, and
当它们在浏览器中时，它们会重新组合在一起。
they get put back together
when they are in the browser.
所以这就像是主要的区别，
So that's like major difference,
使一些HTTP/1实践不是好的HTTP/2实践。
makes some HTTP/1 practices
not good HTTP/2 practices.
和一些HTTP/2实践不好的HTTP/1实践，
And some HTTP/2 practices
not good HTTP/1 practices,
只是关于这些技术如何工作的本质。
just on the very nature of
how the technologies work.
所以，是的，连接所有的JavaScript和
So yeah,
concatenating all of your JavaScript and
CSS到大型单个文件中。
CSS into large single files.
当您只能同时拥有一定数量的连接时，
Useful when you can only have a certain
number of connections at the same time,
当您可以同时发送多个东西和
not useful when you can like
concurrently send multiple things and
然后再把它们拉回来。
then like pull them back apart later.
将图像内联为数据URL，而不是发送图像，您可能会
Inlining images as data URLs instead
of sending the image, you might make
基本的64编码，并将其作为一个巨大的长字符串放入您的CSS文件中。
the basic 64 encoding and put in your
CSS file as a giant, long string.
但是当你可以一次发送多个东西并且你可以有预见性地推送东西时，
But when you can send multiple things at
once and you can predictively push things,
您不能预测性地只推送64位编码的字符串，但是
you can't predictively push just
that 64 bit encoded string, but
你可以有预见性地推送图像。
you could predictively push the image.
那你是做什么的？
So what do you do?
就像，老实说，你测量，对吧？
Like, honestly, you measure, right?
而对于你们，作为前端工程师，
And for you, as front end engineers, for
我们作为前端工程师，我更关心我们的资产战略。
us as front end engineers,
I care more about our asset strategy.
我们制作巨型文件吗？
Do we make giant files?
我们能做小的，对吗？
Do we make tiny little ones, right?
这是关于测量和计算的。
It's about measuring and figuring out.
这不像你打开还是关闭HTTP/1，因为它是向后兼容的。
It's not like do you turn HTTP/1 on or
off, because it is backwards compatible.
就像如果你的服务器支持它，它是不是或者
Like if your server supports it,
it's whether or
不是你选择利用它。
not you choose to take advantage of it.
所以，你测量并计算出来。
And so, you measure and you figure it out.
那么如何获得HTTP/2呢？
So how do you get HTTP/2?
这也是问题的答案，我如何获得CDN？
And this is also the answer to
the question of, how do I get a CDN?
就是你用别人的。
Is you use somebody else's.
所以有一堆服务，你把你的代码放在那里，
So there's a bunch of services,
where you put your code up there,
它是在CDN上，它支持HTTP/2，你可以开箱即用。
it is on a CDN, it is supporting HTTP/2,
you get everything out of the box.
所以剩下的两个是现在的.sh和netlify。
So the left two is now.sh and Netlify.
现在.sh为您提供了一个命令行工具。
Now .sh gives you a command line tool.
您确实喜欢Now Deploy，并且您的应用程序进入云中。
You do like now deploy, and
your app goes up into the cloud.
Netlify实际上也很酷，这就像你可以安装GitHub hook和
Netlify is actually pretty cool too, which
is like you can install GitHub hook and
每当您合并到master中时，它都会部署您的代码。
whenever you merge into master,
it deploys your code.
这就像是我使用的东西，比如我自己的项目和诸如此类的东西。
That is like kind of the things I use
like my own projects and stuff like that.
这可能不是，我肯定有像大公司一样使用这两个
That's probably not, I'm sure there
are like large companies using both these
服务，好像那不是我们七年级时用的。
services, like that's not
what we used in 7th grade.
我们使用亚马逊的云端，这是亚马逊的，
We use Amazon cloud
front which is Amazon's,
我之前给你看的图片是亚马逊CDN。
the picture I showed you
earlier that's Amazon CDN.
你把东西放在S3桶里，你所有的流量都去了云端。
You put stuff in S3 bucket,
all your traffic goes to cloud front.
就像一般情况下一样，您可以配置，可以或
Like generally speaking,
you can configure, you can or
你的应用程序团队或其他什么，可以配置这些后端服务。
your app's team or whatever,
can configure these back end service.
但你也可以直接从货架上拿出解决方案。
But you can also just pull
a solution off the shelf.
CloudFlare是另一个伟大的
Cloudflare is another great
提供支持HTTP/2的CDN的服务。
service that provides a CDN
that is supportive of HTTP/2.
所以就像，你基本上可以选择使用这些服务中的一种，
So like, you can basically if you
choose to use one of these services,
他们都有一些免费的层次。
all of them have some kind of free tier.
但如果你选择使用其中一项服务，
But if you choose to use
one of these services,
基本上就是把这些东西从盒子里拿出来。
you basically get these
things out of the box.
作为前台工程师，你的工作就是思考，好吧，
Your job as a front engineer
is to think about like, okay,
你现在建设的资产是什么，对吗？
what are the assets you're building now,
right?
如果存在这些特性，您还可以利用哪些其他东西？
What other things can you take advantage
of should these features exist?
这张幻灯片在这里，基本上是因为没有人能够看到这些屏幕
This slide is here basically cuz no one's
going to be able to look at those screen
镜头，放大到足够近以获取URL。
shots, zoom in close
enough to get the URLs.
因此，如果您希望稍后引用此内容，请参阅以下URL
So in case you wanna reference this later,
here are URLs for
我刚才说的所有事情。
all the things I just talked about.